<root>
	<services>
		<service name="Sorting">
			<waste-streams>

				<waste-stream name="LDPE">
					<description>
						Low-density polyethylene (LDPE) is a thermoplastic made from the monomer ethylene. It was the first grade of polyethylene, produced in 1933 by Imperial Chemical Industries (ICI) using a high pressure process via free radical polymerization.
					</description>
				</waste-stream>

				<waste-stream name="HDPE">
					<description>
						High-density polyethylene (HDPE) or polyethylene high-density (PEHD) is a thermoplastic polymer produced from the monomer ethylene. It is sometimes called "alkathene" or "polythene" when used for HDPE pipes.[1] With a high strength-to-density ratio, HDPE is used in the production of plastic bottles, corrosion-resistant piping, geomembranes and plastic lumber. HDPE is commonly recycled, and has the number "2" as its resin identification code.
					</description>
				</waste-stream>

				<waste-stream name="Ferrous">
					<description>
						...
					</description>
				</waste-stream>

				<waste-stream name="ConstructionAndDemolition">
					<description>
						The EPA defines this type of waste as “Construction and Demolition (CD) debris is a type of waste that is not included in municipal solid waste (MSW).”[11] Items typically found in CD include but are not limited to steel, wood products, drywall and plaster, brick and clay tile, asphalt shingles, concrete, and asphalt. Generally speaking, construction and demolition waste can be categorized as any components needed to build infrastructures. In 2018, the EPA estimated that the US generated approximately 600 million tons of CD waste. [11]  The waste generated by construction and demolition is often intended to be reused or is sent to the landfill. Examples of reused waste is milled asphalt can be used again for the asphalt mixture or fill dirt can be used to level grade.
					</description>
				</waste-stream>
			</waste-streams>

		</service>
	</services>
</root>